- Uh, what's going on?
- How can I find that...
- Well, what
- What is it, in the government office?
Have you seen the sights? What is it? huh!
Isn't that the moon?
- Isn't it the moon?
- No, what?
- Ome, ome
- Why are you being dragged away?
Just wait and see
The owner stay still and look
Where, huh?
It doesn't go that far.
The moon, ah, ah
- Wow
- No, it's a long sentence.
- Oh my, today
- Go, go, go
It's going to sound like a song
‘Long sentence’?
Oh my, how come, huh?
Hey, what happened to our moon?
Follow me
Why are people so cruel?
If we continue like this, the moon will rise
Hachoga cutting blade tendi
Even a nobleman can’t stop a long sentence.
Wouldn’t Nara know?
Well, Nara might not know, but...
Owner, no way
- No?
- If you are Nara’s son
It's no different from Nara.
Crazy!
Ah, someone pushed me
Don't push, ing
The lady-in-waiting and the nae-gwan who ran away
Are you planning on going in front of the crown prince?
The gentleman who came back to the palace after we left
How do you know our faces?
Don't worry, follow me
Deterioration of the crown prince
Please save my wife
No, but you guys
How did you know I was the crown prince?
Ah, ah, that's over there...
Next to the inner coffin, the military officer is next to him.
Uh, if it comes out
- Hmm...
- I'm sorry for telling you.
My girlfriend
I am in danger of death.
Please show the same generosity as Hae-hae.
Please save my wife, Your Majesty.
Oh, I'm sorry.
In the circumstances of someone I don’t know
I can't just intervene
I'm sorry.
You know my wife too.
- I know?
- Oh, yeah.
We were together last night
This is a backpacker named Bakga Dal.
Where are you?
Where is he?
No, low.
If the sitter finds out...
Where are you, that kid!
let's go
To eat soup
What are you doing, not catching it!
yes!
- Mmm
- Are you ready?
What kind of misfortune is this?
You stopped the long sentence.
That person too
You will not be able to escape responsibility.
You'll get away with it.
- Huh? Nari
- Nari
Hey, people!
No, no.
Oh, no
Ah...
Responsibility
This lady will lose.
Oh, I misunderstood
That kid is not a thief
That's the end
Wait a minute
Leave this alone for a moment
I'm sorry
Did you feel sick?
I have to go back
What do you mean, I'm going back?
It's okay
You can't set fire to Nari.
Do you think this is just your job now?
that face
I clearly said she looked like my wife
But even the mat roll is not enough.
Even the lower plants are cut off.
Are you going to show me?
Even being so mean isn't enough!
The reason for being ‘vulgar’?
Leave Hanyang immediately on this road.
twice again
I can't even step on Hanyang's land
Don't even catch my eye
That's you lowly
It's the price of having that face.
Why should I listen to you?
what?
I'm saying this because I'm worried.
No, actually
I wonder what I'm feeling
What I'm saying is
now please
wake up from this dream
I am not Mrs. Nari in my dream
This is Park Dal, living in reality.
So, you too
Please stop messing around.
stay out of my sight
It looks a bit like a shell
I'm leaving behind like this
If you know that I'm chasing you around
The deceased Mrs. Nari
How dirty do you feel?
Don't speak carelessly
Yes, carelessly or carefully
There won't be anything to say
Now I
Because I have nothing to see.
No need to go, it's resolved.
What does that mean?
Kim Ji-pyeong's wife, who created a false virtuous woman's family
It looks like he planned this out of spite.
I decided to punish him for the crime of treason.
Don't worry
Now that the matter has been resolved
Leave Hanyang immediately
I wasn't hurt
It's a shame
It's okay up there
ha
What are you ashamed of?
I'm ashamed of being mistaken
Everyone ignores me and says I'm lowly
I pretend not to notice and just pass by
Why did you walk straight
Why are you holding my hand?
I was expecting it for no reason
stupidly
ha
Let's go first
I only think bad things about staying here.
I'll keep flying
Where?
'I, Bakdal-i and Eul-eun'
'Prince Jeun and Gap-ui
'The debt that broke the Western clock'
'I poured my bones into dust'?
'Eul comes when Gap comes.
'I go when I have to go'
'The termination of the contract is decided by Party A'
What is this?
Isn’t this a net agreement?
Let’s stay still
The price of the watch you broke...
Oh, yes
Park Gaekju
If this Gaekju is sold,
Can I compensate you?
I took a picture, I took a picture, ing
What do you mean?
Ji should not stay in Hanyang for a long time.
Even if I can't escape
I can't hear it without tears
Is there such a thing?
Why? Because he was a slave who ran away?
Did you know about it too?
How are you all doing it?
♪ While the moon was in pursuit ♪
♪ Losing my parents ♪
No, I want you to know
I even made a song
Wasn’t that what I was calling for, tsk?
Your mouth is right, your mouth is right
So I gave up any thoughts of running away.
until i come back
Wait in Hanyang
You know if I run away, right?
po
degrees
Cheong
It's so bad, Mr.
Where are you going?
To propose
Oh my, oh my
Oh my, that's right
Uh, what should I do?
-What should I do, kid...
- Oh, really, kinda!
- Ugh?
- Stay still, you're crazy!
My daughter is forever
I might just lie still
How can I stay still?
The evening came and went like this.
If you get crazy
Even if our moon comes quickly...
You do?
Put it on
Oh my, our moon
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
- Ome, ome
- Oh, why, why, why?
Wow, why is my father like that again?
It's the moon!
Why? Why, why are you doing this, huh?
no, we
I thought the moon was going to cut off your leg...
How did you know?
I'm sorry, everyone stop crying.
Go in, go in, yeah, pop, pop
draw, draw
- Hey, hey, come in.
- Be careful, be careful.
- Leeing, draw, draw
- What should I do, legs?
child, sit, sit
- Uh, draw, draw.
- Uh, sit down, sit down, sit down.
Oh my, oh my, draw it
- By the way.
- Yes
People called tusks and fathers
Because I knew everything
- Sitting in this warm field
- Huh?
I was just waiting quietly, huh?
After coming to the front and waiting
I should have come with support or something.
Oh my, oh my
i broke my legs
It should have been cut, right?
I matched my father’s height
You should have come
- Right?
- What, what?
Oops, I was wrong.
I was wrong, oops
Ah, yes, the crown prince...
fish oil
no
We met you yesterday
That nari, huh?
That person...
And the moon is for that child
The fact that I am the crown prince
Please don't put your foot down
If you know my identity
In the meantime, I committed
worry about rudeness
I'm going to lie down sick
Do we also think of ourselves as runaway slaves?
Just go somewhere safe
I told you to wait
Take responsibility yourself
I'll bring you back safely
How does Tusk know who he is?
Oh my, your tusks
I put my mind to it and ejaculated
Please save me that Narihunty.
The tusks
You ejaculated?
Kid...
I don't even know that
strange
Obviously that baggage seller’s father
It looked like an inner coffin
It felt exactly like that
I think this is already my 38th answer.
How can a naekwan take care of her children?
- Ah...
- Stop it.
It's uncomfortable for me too.
But why am I
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
The first thing I said harshly was
While doing that
- I can hear everything.
- Yes
Oh, I said it out loud so you could hear it.
Don't come
'Don't come'...
If you don't meet me
That backpacker
How can you come to me first?
I'm afraid I'll go
In the future too
I'm afraid you'll run like a crazy person.
Because I hurt you so much
I won't be able to go anymore
this way
Leave Hanyang immediately
That's you lowly
It's the price of having that face.
bad guy
Am I a swallow?
Why did you fix my knee?
Why are you protecting my legs?
I'm confused as to whether it's Nolbu or Heungbu
Oh no
This is the world's left-wing sensitivity
There is nothing I can do about this woman.
Lady Woohee’s personality
Where is normal?
Father and daughter look exactly alike
- Ugh
What does that mean?
Woohee and Jwasang are father and daughter.
What...
Why don't you ask?
I think I know
for contusion
Knowing my desire for revenge
Revealing that the woman on the left is
It must have been difficult
Isn’t it truly an indifferent sky?
I can't believe you're pulling a prank like this.
So
Are you just going to blame the sky?
I'm indifferent and just complaining
I become destitute
Are you just going to watch?
If you do
What should I do?
Didn't you make a promise?
You won't let go of my hand
Let's run away, come out
Wherever my father goes
Think you won't find it?
More than anything, I hate it
I gave up everything I had
It's like falling into the abyss
It's not in my plans.
If you don't become a national governor,
This is the father who will abandon me.
He is the father who will harm the great army.
So please make a decision.
now
Are you talking about rebuttal?
Anyway, the gold award
It's no different from rebuttal
Find your original place
Yes? degradation
don't call me that
He is a crown prince who was dethroned a long time ago.
Queen Jangjeong
If you hadn't been framed like that
In the throne room
He wouldn't have been dethroned
Definitely a jerk
It must have been the Grand Prince's.
I have never wanted that position even once.
All I wanted was
Unless it's a jerk
hope for me
have me
I'm sorry
Geary
Are you going to abandon me?
I'm sorry
What a cowardly man.
- Jericha
- Yes, ma'am.
Bring in the palanquin workers.
Are you going to Hanyang?
yes
Fu
I'm sorry to tell you
The Crown Prince said
He told me to come pick him up in person.
Got it
yes
If you do it
Please send a message to Woohee.
I will tell that to the crown prince.
Directly serve the women’s meal
Bring me here?
yes
I am staying at Sinjusa Temple in Yeongdeok.
The road is not difficult
The woman on the left is mentally and physically immature.
Didn't you say you were recuperating?
not nursing
I'm in training
Still to become the Crown Princess
They say I don't have any virtue
I've been staying at a temple.
He said, ‘That’s enough.’
Please give it to me directly.
Ah, recently I wrote a long sentence.
I heard you blocked it.
Not long ago, the case of false virtuous women was solved.
I think it was called subcompensation.
But the sub-compensator is a woman.
yes
I went out to play and got noticed.
I helped him because he seemed pitiful.
why
Did you notice that woman?
lump
I'm sure you haven't forgotten my advice, right?
The sinner's grave is coming
If you look for it here, you won't find it.
I lost both my mother and my wife
What is more to be afraid of?
So my advice is
Please engrave it in your heart.
Except my girlfriend
All the women you love
will die
Like this
How could you possibly forget?
always
I'm keeping this in mind
I love this greenhouse
Pronunciation and temperature
Memories accumulated here
Everything is warm
Oh my mom
When he died after being falsely accused
Abama, please
Mama’s injustice
Please release me
Abama!
Please...
everything you see
I prayed to everything invisible
Oh my mom
Oh my!
Dethrone the crown prince
Imprisoned in Sinjusa Temple
Uh, oh my
Are you okay?
no one is on my side
When it wasn't done
When my family and heaven abandoned me
It had to be you, it had to be you
You had cold hands
Are you okay?
cold
sorry
Are you okay?
it hurts?
It's okay
It was nice because it was cold
My heart was so hot it throbbed.
I'm glad you're safe
I thought then
my sky
My hands are cold
one now
Be someone else's sky
It becomes another man's world
While living
Don't be cold anymore
Even the hands
Mind too
Even then, sometimes I can't help it
On cold days
Come and rest in this greenhouse
It's all yours now
A national wedding in advance
Congratulations
Poor mom
Now go back to Boryeong
so easily
Are you saying you are letting me go?
now
'Cause I don't need you anymore
Rather, if you are here
Things get more out of whack
Is that true?
I'm not going to say anything else right now?
instead
do me a favor
Well, I mean a favor.
If you cross the line, it becomes coercion.
It's a threatening issue.
Depending on what kind of request this is...
I haven't torn up the contract yet.
The level of ‘hard work’ is different.
This is it
I have to work hard
What is it? Yeah
- Hello everyone.
- Hey
Who are you?
Oh, you're new here.
I serve the acting chieftain of Yukuijeon.
I am Hanyang Sangsang Cha’s servant.
You are
Permission to enter the upper chamber
I heard you have a servant.
Could it be you
Is your car Eunwoo?
That's right
I'm Cha Eunwoo
Um, come on in.
Thank you
Now
Let's go in
yes
This bracelet is made of red stone.
With the best new red promotional stone
If you have this, you will have health and wealth
Wisdom follows
Fear in my heart
It's a precious thing that gets rid of
And in all dangers and difficulties
that you can escape
It has such great meaning
Oh, that's it, that's enough
It has no meaning at all
Prepare with expensive items
Yes, I understand.
So how long will you be ready?
Well, get ready within an hour.
We are leaving today
Yes? Right now?
There's so much to prepare, right?
Just 15 Ikwisa members were formed.
I will come back in a simple way
- Chabihae
- Yes, lower.
Oh, is it bokbunja?
um
Write it
Ikwis are tired
Please rest for a while.
Yeah, I guess so.
Is there a place to rest nearby?
Look it up
yes, degradation
Ah!
ah!
Are you going to Shinjusa Temple?
why?
Today's errand is a secret.
You shouldn't tell anyone
Why?
Well, I’m sending it to Jeongin.
Can I have a love letter?
I understand
It's a secret
That Nari
Where are you going?
Ha, I have a secret too.
Oh no
It looks a bit like a shell
I'm leaving behind like this
If you know that I'm chasing you around
The deceased Mrs. Nari
How dirty do you feel?
Hey, that...
You know, that...
Well, last time that
When it comes to long sentences...
Um, mmmmmm
If you both go to Shinjusa Temple,
Shall we accompany you?
huh?
Narido Shinjusa Gasindaeyu?
Why is there a new drink?
He is going to meet his fiancé.
Ah...
Did you have a fiancé?
Well, no...
Well, well, well, so...
He who loses
I need to pack some luggage.
It's just that the crown prince is a brat.
Why don't we add rooms together, huh?
What are you doing?
The whole city already knows
No, but this guy
Mr. I
Are you going to accompany that backpacker?
Well, there is only one way to go.
Won't we be forced to go together?
Well, that's what I'm saying...
To the members of the National Guard
Don't reveal your true identity.
I ordered it
No, what I'm trying to say is
How do you know...
the other day
That backpacker
Knowing the identity of the lower class
Aren't you concerned?
thank you
This bastard saw that
I need to learn, hmm.
degradation
where are you going now
don't forget
Mistress
ha
Twisting?
Are you just cracking up without even looking at me?
True
Normally, if that happens,
Don't move
The men walk
You got on the plane, Eosa Nari.
Such a peerless beauty is your fiancé.
A peerless beauty
The reason you’re pretty is because you’re prettier, right?
No, uh, how
Are there all these Buddha statues in a place like this?
Hey...
If the Buddha statue is not in the temple
Where is it?
Where are you?
What is this strange story all of a sudden?
I'm surprised, Mr.
There are precious ladies here
Do you think a lot of people come here?
Also, Mr. Jwasangdaek.
I heard you are here
That's Jwasangdaek's wife.
Hey, then the daughters of Mr. Jwasangdaek.
Looks like everyone is here
‘Daughters’?
I am the only daughter without a man.
That guy over there
Quite a bit
Do you think this is a sincere wish?
If you see that you don't stand up even when you see me
Yes, it must be done
Because it's a prayer
I have something to say
Shall we meet at the edge of the cliff in one hour?
Hey
After all, it’s the edge of a cliff.
Why?
Are you going to push me away?
I won't do such stupid things
there
The scenery overlooking it is spectacular.
You came this far
Enjoy that level of charm.
Is she a good person?
How does it look?
Does this sound like a question?
I'm a bad person
Thank goodness
If he was a good person
I almost felt uncomfortable
I'm bad too
I'm so glad
Just keep doing what you were doing.
Ah
Don't try too hard
Buddha is
Bad people pray
For not listening well
I...
Ha, what is it again...
Who are you?
Prince Jeun sent it.
Are you the lady of Jwasangdaek Jwasang?
Prince Jeun asked me to tell you this.
Wow, I...
Maybe it's because it's a mountain, but the wind is harsh.
My eyes are all sore.
Well then, I'll just go and see.
stop
you go this way
Go straight down the mountain
Huh? The sun has gone down...
go
Is it the cost of errands?
Wow...
go
yes
Are you here?
Come on and have a drink
oh oh
- Oh...
- Oh my, my, my, my.
Ugh
- That's right, you guy.
- Ah...
Who looks like that
Do you want to eat bokbunja?
Oh, and I don't even chew it.
Because I swallow it with honey
Well, will there be any leftovers, huh?
Ugh, tsk.
No, why do I
Because it’s good for men
Are you going crazy like that?
I really don't understand
The interior is also in-house.
Oh! Oh...
What are you doing?
Huh
Your words were inconsiderate.
What, why?
It's not wrong
That's right
Not everything is correct
Your father was my teacher
Are you my teacher?
These are my father’s teachings.
Oh my, is it already one o’clock?
I need to go for a walk
Everyone, eat well and rest well.
yes
Oh no
Where is this guy?
Can't you see?
Oh my, Nari!
Oh, by any chance.
Didn't you see it?
Hey there
Ah
What did you say just now?
I said I wouldn't do it.
This national wedding
The meaning of this national wedding
I don't think you understand
This is not a marriage between the two of us.
The top left is the seat of the national ball.
I want power from the left
This is
The reason for our national marriage
In the meantime, I don't have my heart
This is why I don't have a national wedding.
Is my heart even there in the meantime?
So, national marriage
Please step down.
How about this?
i want you
Should I love you sincerely?
The women I love
I will definitely die
them
Who killed him?
Chi
Oh, you look so unfamiliar.
Well, I'm going to leave now.
To my teacher,
I will never go to Hanyang again.
Please tell me not to worry
I hope you are doing well too.
Going to be burned in a flower pot soon
There is also a woman
Why did Da-jeong get nervous for no reason?
Confuse people
Now that means
Do you know what it means?
Don’t I know you too well?
So
You left me empty
Aren’t you trying to get hit?
To get revenge on my father
Sorry but
I don't think so.
Living as someone else's tool
Now I'm inflamed
Actually
I'm not even sorry
I have made my intentions clear enough.
Let's go in
You must have been tired so far.
Have a long sleep
Oh...
Huh?
Ouch!
The tiger has one arm
You'll have to let it go, right?
I become food for the tiger
Something should be lying around on the mountain path
'Ah, you are kind because of me.
I said, ‘The vice president is dead.’
tears of repentance
I'm about to spill it
By the way
Eosa Nari is in this sexual relationship.
What do you know, what do you not know?
Still
Should I have said hello?
Thank you for saving me a long sentence when I folded.
I couldn't even say thank you
The kid left?
yes
I won't go to Hanyang.
He told me not to worry.
No, how can you not worry?
No matter how clear the waterways and mountain paths are,
Even if you're a backpacker, it's the same.
How rough are the mountains here?
Just without any fear
Wait a minute, where is he now?
Ugh
Who sent them?
First of all, I somehow
I'll try to stop it
Take refuge with the lady
Don't be bluff
You alone can do this much
How are you going to handle it all?
save me
Didn't you say you wanted to kill me?
If you want to kill me, I have to be alive.
Come on, come on
just wait a moment
I will be back soon
Hey
child
Hey, uh
Hehe!
ruler!
In this
never come out
Don't make any noise
In this situation now
Are you laughing?
Isn't it funny?
The person who said he was going to kill me a while ago
Saving me
I have to live like you said
Tomorrow or next year
I won't kill you with my own hands
So buy it today
Hey!
eww!
Ouch!
Ugh
Oh Shin-won!
Ouch!
Yes, lower!
Ugh
- Ah
- Ugh
Ugh, ah, uh...
Shin-won Oh, left-wing committee member!
yes, degradation
From now on, I will do my best
splatter
‘Splash’?
Ugh...
Ah...
If you go a little further, there is a beacon station.
- Be patient.
- Yes
- Let's go over there.
- Yes!
let's go
Ha, hoo
Ha, kid
Until we reach the beacon tower
Did you calculate it?
I need to start a fire
This is why
People need to learn
The suffering of the people
It finally makes sense
Don't play with Yoon Se-dol from now on.
It's cold
A dagger flies into my chest and stabs me.
I think it will hit my back, not my chest.
Uh, ah, ugh
Ouch!
Ugh
Huh
Degradation!
Ugh
ha
Please keep the minimum number of people
Don't tell me to go
It's hard for me
The harder it is, the bigger it gets
Anything bigger means aging.
Ah, ah!
Shin Won-ah
Poetry, Shin Won-ah
Poor...
no it doesn't work
No, Shinwon.
You shouldn't go here.
You can't go here, Shinwon.
yes
It's going to be hard
Close your eyes
I, I will support you and take you with me
Ugh...
Deterioration, deterioration...
left wing, left wing
Left wing, left wing!
Ah, left wing...
Please open your eyes
- Ah...
- Mom, it's a surprise.
Good luck, leftist...
- Deterioration, degradation...
- Oh, thank goodness.
Poor...
My dear, why are you looking for me there?
He was shot in front of me.
Damn, uh...
Left wing, this
I... it's not true, is it?
Left wing...
No, right?
uh?
lowering!
Poor...
charge
The woman on the left falls down the cliff.
The decline is falling
I testified that I saw it in person.
So now let's go
Stop waiting...
In the midst of this
To make Prince Jeun the crown prince
don't speak
Wouldn't it?
Loyalty worried about resignation from Jongmyo Shrine
do not blaspheme
And in the current situation
In addition to Jeundaegun
Is there no other way?
Your Majesty Boryeong Now
Since you are a little over forty
All you have to do is have a national wedding.
Ha, you guys are amazing.
In front of His Majesty who lost his son
How dare you mention the national spirit?
They are so ugly
Uh-huh, be polite!
What, ugly, ugly?
Hey, who's really ugly, huh?
stop!
How can one country
Those called Daesin
Can't you see?
I apologize.
Chief left, um
- Wow, it's a pear.
- Hey
Ugh sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss
Ugh
Wow
No, there's something like a human corpse here...
Oh my my my my my my my!
Isn't it a corpse?
Geary, geary tiger
We came this far, uh, seed
Well then
Why is it okay when only the bones remain?
Ah, oh, oh, oh
Ugh
Ugh...
Huh? lily?
lily!
Come to your senses, please!
what's this?
Ah, Mr.
With Sang-daek Jwasang’s daughter
When you get married
Why get shot, why do you want to get shot
- Uh, uh, fish oil, fish oil...
- It's mom!
Have you not seen this person?
I must have been shot in the chest.
Are you mom?
Write...
Well, you
If you see it
You have to inform the government office, definitely.
Ying, Ying, take care.
- Over there
- That clap, that clap.
Isn't it there?
Please look for it properly.
- Okay
- What crime did you commit?
If you know that I was shot at the government office,
I'll search the doctor's office first.
If I don't go, are you going to run after me?
Still got caught
Rather than die without receiving treatment
This one is better, yeah
That's it, ing
Oh no
Ah...
Uh, uh, ah
Uh, uh, uh...
Why doesn't this stop? Why doesn't it stop?
Ah, oh, oh, oh
- Ah...
- Oh my, oh my.
Oh my, how, oh my
Wait a minute, oh my
Oh my, why are you like this?
Why doesn't this stop?
Oh my, oh my
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Just hold on a little longer
Now
Ouch!
Ah...
Ouch! Ugh...
Oh my, oh my
I'm sorry, Nari.
Ouch!
Shut up!
I'm sorry
- Ah
- Ugh...
Really like this
If Prince Jeun is installed as crown prince,
Isn't it a big deal?
If we push for national marriage now,
The main award himself
He is a great man who will end his life.
Chief Left Officer
It is difficult to choose Jeundaegun as the second best option.
The stakes are high
So far, the main award
What I was able to swing
It's because the crown prince had a weakness.
Right now, Geumsang doesn’t have that.
Then like this
Are you planning to wait and see?
If the crown prince died
Prince Jeun takes over the dragon statue.
It's a natural procedure.
Where is the gold medal?
Did you sit on the table when it was your turn?
Those words...
Je, Prince Jeun
Are you saying you are going to kill me?
Father
Woohee is here
What did you say just now?
I killed the crown prince
Made Prince Jeun the Crown Prince
To sit next to him.
You can't believe it...
Yes, this is my lover
How dare you break my will
Are you destroying my dreams?
To become my country
how much effort did you put in
Even if you know
Why did you do something like this?
Father's meaning
I have no intention of breaking it.
Made Prince Jeun the Crown Prince
It will be the Crown Princess
Thus, the national emblem of this country
will be
Naturally, Father will also become a national leader.
who told you
Did I tell you to think about it?
I decided to do that
From now on
You should know
I am not my father’s tool.
That my father is my tool
The gold award goes to my father.
You may have made it
next royal road
Next royal road
I make it
Will this be a treason or useful?
It's in my hands
Are you awake?
You in front of me
Is it a dream or a cause?
Whether it's a dream or a wish
i die
I don't care if this is hell
I wanted to see it like this
My Yeonwol-ah
I, I...
Oh, not yet
Hey there, spirit.
I guess you haven't come back yet, huh?
Well, I even got shot.
Yes, yes, yes
- Oh my, ah.
- Ah, ah...
Did you save me?
Good job
You just had a hard time.
Nursing for 15 days and 15 nights
Wow, I almost died.
What? ‘Full moon’?
Hmm, did you do well?
I have to go to Hanyang right away.
Get me a horse.
My case will be generous.
W Yeongdeok, huh?
Let’s get on a horse and go to Hanyang with this body?
This is just the grim reaper
It's like, 'Take me away.'
I'll take care of it myself
Hurry and get me a horse.
If it's that urgent
Why don't you send a letter?
Wow
‘Messenger’?
A messenger to Hanyang!
Even when I'm sleeping, I wake up
uh!
Massinger!
- Even if you hold a spoonful of rice in your mouth
- I'm a messenger from Hanyang!
Jump up
Massinger!
Even while unpacking my clothes
Jump up and run
Joseon’s best contact network!
Massinger!
Is this the dogmatism of the woman on the left?
Does it mean left top?
Have a long sleep
It was a murder notice
Come out and see me
This, ow
why is it so high
Aww, aww, hey, aww, hey, aww
again
What are you doing there?
Aren't you coming down?
The guy who owes money
No, he owes money
Why did you believe and sent me alone?
So I
Didn't you say you would give a reward?
The role of this swallow is
As long as Mr. Park delivers it.
I'm still out there
I can't decide if it's Heungbu or Nolbu.
I will give you Mr. Musin Park.
I couldn't worry
Wait a minute
What are you talking about?
Oh, really
How do you ride it?
Wow, really
catch
Even if you're nervous, endure it
Because I can’t afford to even consider your heart.
Trembling
Why are you nervous?
Ha!
fish oil, fish oil
Whoa, whoa
Ugh
Wow
What are you doing now?
Get off
two days
You ran without stopping.
If things continue like this, at least you can stay here.
Whether I die or not is up to me.
no
This is the life I saved
My life is mine.
in front of my eyes
Even if I die, I can’t look at my dead face.
Then I'll disappear from your sight
No...
Uh, oh my
Mr. I
Yeah, uh
I was going alone
Die or die, Mr.
After shedding a lot of blood, I ended up becoming food for animals.
Either die or not...
My lord
How do we get here...
Didn't I make a promise?
let's go
To eat soup
What kind of chick am I, huh?
Are you Mongolian?
A cold sweat formed steadily,
Wow
Rise up
eyes and lips
I can see everything, even the red thing
Ah, how could I just leave?
Stop!
Stop it, you idiot!
Oh my...
Wow, Mr.
Stop, uh...
Are you stupid?
If you fall
I have to stop and wait
Cry because it hurts
Get angry and tell me to come back!
Why are you running again, why!
Have you thought about it?
I don't want anything from Ji.
You protected my legs.
So, I'm having a blast
The swallow is not going anywhere without Heungbu.
not me
you caught me
You came running to me
So save me
Do your best to protect me
It's a person
The Crown Prince is alive?
It got annoying.
You
Are you sure you can come back?
The truth doesn't matter
I saw it while passing by
When I saw it, I stopped, and when I stopped, I realized
My heart
I hope you survive this time
Please
Ah, Nari
- Please save me
- Come here.
It's !
Let Prince Jeun sit on the throne.
And next to it
I will sit down.
What should I do?
From Yeongdeok to Hanyang
all the way
Ambush the warbands
Crown Prince
So that you can never come back